Once upon a time, there was a handsome slave.
What bound him were not heavy chains, but the love of a princess.
Every day, every night, the princess whispered her love to the slave,
and the slave responded in kind.
Bound body, bound emotions.
The slave or the princess, which of them is really the one who is unable to move?
Let go of me. I can walk by myself.
No!
That's right. Princess Tutu helped me and then…
Binding my wounds. What kind of a useless ch…
Hey.
Oh, Fakir. How are you?
Don't give me that. Why are you still Tutu?
What? Oh, I thought it might be bad if I went in the boys' dorm looking like normal.
Was that weird?
No. Sorry for having troubled you with this.
It was no trouble. Oh, you're able to get up then.
Hey, listen. This doesn't mean I plan on cooperating with you.
But you're going out to look for Muto, aren't you?
We could at least cooperate on that, right? Let's look for Muto together.
You can forget about everything. All you need to fill that void is here in my arms.
No one shall enter here. It shall just be you and me. So I am the only one that you have to give your love to. Now tell me that you love only me.
I love only you, Krehi. Nobody else.
Honestly?
Honestly.
What's that? How much?
If you love me, then smile for me. Don't you remember the festival?
How?
Have you regressed to the doll you used to be? Because I withdrew that piece of your heart?
Have you shut out all your other emotions because of that?
If that's true, then fine. If you're going to love someone else better for you not to love anyone.
It's your fault, you know. You wouldn't so much as look at me when I love you so much.
No. You're not the one to blame.
That's right. If you hadn't begun to regain your heart, everything would have progressed like it should have.
I wouldn't have remembered that I... that I was really a crow.
It's all the fault of that nuisance.
A pest like that.
The sooner we're rid of her, the better for us.
A single prince has no need of two princesses.
Right?
Herr Drosselmeyer?
What? Impossible! Did I just hear her call my name?
You're watching from somewhere, yes?
You have guts to call on me.
Guts enough to offer you the best story ever.
What? Really?
The best of stories demands the best of endings.
And for that, I need a worthy stage.
You're right. And I have a stage I've been saving.
A lake that no one has visited in 200 years.
Do allow me to show you the way.
Mewto! He's not here either.
He's not around.
Of course he is.
It's just that we haven't been able to find him.
Hm?
Oh! The lesson room!
Huh?
He might be dancing there right now, huh?
And why's that?
Huh?
Because Mewto loves to dance, and that's where…
I don't think he is.
He might be dancing there right now, huh?
And why's that?
Huh? Because Mewto loves to dance, and that's where…
I don't think he'll be there.
But, but the last time he was taken, he was back before we knew it, right?
So, I thought it might be the same this time.
Besides, I can't think of anywhere else.
We can check it out. We've nothing to lose.
Huh?
Oh, wait for me!
Yeah?
Hey…
The school sure is quiet on Sundays.
I guess.
Is that Miyuto?
Hey, I get to see you.
What? Where? What? What?
Huh?
Whoa!
Oh?
I can see you.
Huh?
What?
Who dares to intrude upon my Sunday practice?
Oh, Miss Duck.
This time I will punish you for disturbing my tireless effort.
I will! Have you marry me right now!
I'm so sorry!
What were you doing?
But... but...
Hello there!
Miuto?
So Miuto's okay! Thank goodness he—
Wait! You know the story of the Prince and the Raven?
It's a tale of a brave prince who battles a monster raven.
There was a knight whom the prince trusted,
but this same knight was torn in two by the claws of the raven.
Without the knight even landing a single blow with his sword,
a useless wretch who could only talk of protection.
That's why the prince suffered such hardship.
The raven had leapt out of the story.
Alone he pursued it, and alone he sealed it away.
Of his own will, he used a forbidden power.
That's right.
The prince drew his sword and took his very own heart out of his body.
What? How? He took it—he took it out himself?
Oh, it's true.
What? True?
You don't know anything, do you, Duck?
What do you know about Princess Tutu?
Princess Tutu? Nothing! I mean, I don't know!
You see, in The Prince and the Raven, Princess Tutu is only presented in a few sentences.
A miserable existence which none of the characters of the story wanted to take on.
An insignificant existence which even the story left by the wayside.
Someone who could never hope to catch the prince's eye.
A little added flourish.
Oh, poor thing.
But Rue, why are you telling me this story now?
So you still haven't figured it out?
Rue doesn't even really exist.
What?
Now then, you have finally figured it out, Princess Tutu.
Princess... Crazy?
No way! You can't be, cause you're my friend!
We used to chat together and dance together and—
Come on, knock it off.
That's true.
But the time has come to put an end to all that foolishness.
Rue, please!
I only came to retrieve something the prince left behind, so I'll take my leave now.
Left behind?
It is not something for a mere failure of a knight to have in his custody.
The prince's sword, but when did she get—
Rue, no!
Hurry up and come rescue the prince!
Oh, Miss Eero!
Miss Eero!
Water is drawn to fire,
Fire to darkness,
Darkness to silence.
Come, let us go.
Go where?
To where you must go.
We must go.
Aw...
This place...
Uh, Miss Eero?
Miss Eero?
It's locked.
This place, uh, Ms. Adol?
You can go to where the Prince and Krehi are from here.
An entrance here?
Go on.
Thanks a lot, Ms. Adol, for always being so kind to me.
This is not kindness.
Huh?
Puppets follow the pull of their strings.
Puppets?
Yes, I am a puppet.
I possess neither feelings nor a heartbeat.
But, Ms. Adol, you've taught me all sorts of things and you've been so friendly.
That's why I think of you like a...
You think of me like that because that was the role I was appointed.
My orders end here.
Now go on, Duck.
Whose orders are that?
Miss Adol?
Now go on, Duck.
Thanks a lot.
We'll go now.
Duck.
Such a warm face.
Such soft skin.
Miss Adol, I...
Now, you must hurry.
Okay, let's go.
Good grief.
You's a puppet too long.
They start getting attached to things other than strings.
Things like people's feelings.
Don't you forget, your role is to add a glow to the story in my place.
That's about all you're capable of doing anyhow.
Not knowing your place in the world is dangerous, you know.
Scary.
Scary!
Ow!
Idiot, walk towards the middle.
You're already careless enough as it is.
Huh?
Wow, this place is kind of incredible.
Oh!
Okay, okay, eyes forward.
Whoa!
Um, you really are Princess Tutu, aren't you?
Huh?
Yeah, what of it?
I thought Princess Tutu was more, uh, you know.
Huh?
Never mind.
Say, Fakir.
What is it?
N-nothing, never mind.
What the heck?
If you didn't want to say, just keep your mouth shut.
Oh, no, it's not like that.
But just so you know, I don't think you're no good as a knight or anything.
What are you getting at?
I'm not really trying to get at anything.
It's just, I didn't think you were very nice when we first met.
But now I feel like I know you a little better.
I'll say this right now.
I have no intention of cooperating with you.
I'll help Mewtwo in my own way.
End of story.
Hmm.
I know that.
Wow, you know?
Hmm?
Never mind, it's nothing.
What is your problem?
Quit stopping in the middle of your sentences.
Well, the truth is that I never thought about things like, what do I like about Mewtwo?
Oh.
The first time I saw Mewtwo, it was mostly me just thinking he was handsome.
But when I looked closer, his eyes looked so lonely.
And I thought if I became Princess Tutu, then maybe I could do something for him.
At the start, that's all there really was to it.
But now, I...
Damn it!
Fuck him!
Run!
Fuck!
Come on!
Idiot!
Sorry, are you hurt at all?
It's a miracle I'm not.
What is this place?
I guess we'll just have to climb back up.
Uh...
Oh!
We might be able to get out through the water.
I could go check it out if I became a bird, but...
It's covered in moss.
I doubt we can climb it.
Damn!
Since it's Vakir...
Vakir?
What is it?
One time, when I had lost this necklace, you held onto it for me.
Remember, Vakir?
Huh?
What about it?
Would you hold onto it again?
What the heck is this all about?
Here.
Huh?
What was that?
Where did she go?
Quack!
A duck?
She just...
So then, this wasn't a pendant for her to become Tutu?
It can't be that duck.
Sorry, you've caught me at a bad moment.
But...
Just so you know, I don't think you're no good as a knight or anything.
She saw...
Me crying.
No way!
She isn't drowning now, is she?
Can Ducks even drown, though?
Knowing her, she might.
What?
Idiot!
Why did you...
Why did you not tell me?
You shouldn't hide things like that!
What?
Quit playing dirty, you...
You say that, but it's not like I revealed it to you because I wanted to!
It's just easier when I'm a bird to check, Smalls!
You saw?
No.
More importantly, what did you see?
Shouldn't you be bringing that up first?
How can I, when...
Don't stand!
We can make it to the other side, through the water!
The water down that way smelled different, so there's probably a lake up ahead.
See?
It looks like it goes deeper.
That's probably where Mewto is.
Were you okay back there, Fakir?
Huh?
What is it?
A duck as Princess Tutu, huh?
What?
I have something you'll want to hear.
Back when I was still a brat, when I was reading The Prince and the Raven to Mewto,
the thing that he showed the strongest interest in was neither what happened to himself nor
the raven, but what happened to Tutu, about whom only a little was actually written.
He wanted to hear over and over again the part where Tutu turns into a speck of light
and then vanishes.
His sudden desire to regain his heart most likely stems from Tutu's role in returning
it.
But they were saying Mewto took his heart out himself.
That's the kind of guy he is.
Well, you see, protecting the small and the weak, that is Mewto's single greatest desire,
and to fulfill that, he'll cast off any regard for himself.
Even the loss of his heart couldn't tear that out of him.
That's Mewto.
Let's go.
Right.
Finally you've come.
I'm tired of waiting.
Mewto!
Welcome to the stage I've been saving.
Now tell me the best story that was ever told.
Tell it to me with no regard for your lives.
Please stop this malevolence now!
Agreed.
Let us put an end to it.
The Prince's feeling of love is right here.
The heart that loves people, that loves all the world, yet belongs to no one.
And I wonder, you or me, which one of us will it choose?
Whose words will it be drawn to once we've both laid our hearts bare?
If the shard chooses you, I'll return it and the Prince.
So then, why don't you speak to it of what burns in your heart?
Well, Princess Tutu?
No!
I love you.
But why do we have to fight each other this way? Because we both...
Ultimately, you were only borrowing the power of Princess Tutu.
You are merely a sham of a princess, eh, duck?
You alone and nobody else could accept Princess Tutu's fate. So smiley.
You are my true princess.
Yes, I am your one true princess.
The real me is just a duck with no powers of my own.
But if I have you, I can transform!
All you children who love stories, come gather round!
Mercury 8
It's for three to the second one.
It's the car, yeah.
Why are you so focused on this sakit title?
That is correct?
It's just a statement.
You have to grab family cola, PC, want the keto,
put your fortunately back on the moment a day of surprise,
and apparently I'm Miss Plus últimji on that.
And eventually I turned to a film I'm Miss you both in and I'm Moon,
I headed to a arbeiten tie for itself and then I'll let you go to that
Starting with an armor on the table nicely